CONTACT

(2)

+34 659 853 780

 \bowtie

marc.castells.guell@gmail.com

https://castlemark.github.io

Barcelona, 08021

EDUCATION

MULTIMEDIA ENGINEERING

(Minor in Videogames) La Salle URL, Barcelona

2015 - 2019

SPORTS TECHNICIAN

(Alpine Skiing) **Joviat. Manresa**

2015 -2016

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native Catalan: Native

English: Fluid

(FCE, B2 Equivalent)

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Advanced Level:

- C
- C++
- C#
- Java
- RxJava
- GDScript

Intermediate Level:

- Python
- SQL
- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- PHP

Marc Castells

CURRICULUM VITAE

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Student in Multimedia Engineering (4th year) with 5 years of experience as a trainer and section manager of an alpine skiing team. My most outstanding skills are game design, programming and usability. I consider myself a versatile, organized and proactive person. I am interested in consolidating and expanding my knowledge in order to develop my professional career within the Videogames industry.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer, Intern

06/2018 - 10/2018

Scopely,

Barcelona, España

Responsible for designing an app to work in conjunction with the company's ecosystem for the purposes of metadata processing and customer segmentation.

Head of Section

11/2016 - 04/2018

CANM-Cerdanya, Puigcerdà, España

Responsibilities:

- Planning of the training season based on competition schedule.
- Coordination between the different teams on all Ski Resorts where we operate (Grandvalira, Masella).
- Coach for alpine ski team (ages 12 to 16).

Coach, Alpine Skiing

11/2013 - 04/2018

CANM-Cerdanya,

Puigcerdà, España

Responsibilities:

- Coach for the interclubs section on Grandvalira, Andorra, whose athletes participate in the Catalan league of clubs.
- Production and follow-up on technical, tactical and theoretical training.
- Communication and coordination for events such as competitions.

TOOLS & GAME ENGINES

Tools:

- Git
- Gradle
- Docker
- 3ds Max
- SolidWorks
- Office

Game Engines:

- Unity
- Godot Engine

GAME JAMS

So far I've participated in the following game jams:

- Barcelona Games World Jam 2017
- Not Only Games Jam by King 2018
- GMTK Game Jam 2018

You'll find the games made in these Game Jams on my website: https://castlemark.github.io

MOBILITY & AVAILABILITY

My availability is from mid-June'19 part-time.

My area of mobility is the Metropolitan Area of Barcelona.